[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
um
[Music]
so
um
[Music]
peace
um
[Music]
thank you
my face
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
traditional manchester
from a wave
[Music]
now
is
[Music]
oh
thank you
[Music]
bye
oh
[Music]
okay
thirty-three
[Music]
but turning your one thousand pesos into
one hundred thousand is food
when a person is dead written unexpected
critical energy if only she or he had
one a gift of two thousand could be from
friends i give of 20 000 to different
relatives i keep from doing two hundred
thousand different parents but the gift
of two million is perfect insurance
so a person no matter how capable he is
in a lifetime cannot avoid
getting sick
but getting into an accident so do
something today that your future self
will thank you for expect the best
prepare for those
that's all
so thank you
no it's like an investment you know and
he named him but it will be invested
into global markets global markets
peso indonesia philippine market like
bti and quan but we are going to invest
as blue bunny so fw 31
so
and then
so we are located in security bank
no business part
uh lost
[Music]
is
and chat
[Music]
you
hey
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
uh
okay
[Music]